[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the population of Eilat according to the Israel Central Bureau of Statistics end of 2004 census?", "correct_answer": "45,800", "incorrect_answers": ["179,400", "79,200", "129,700"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Bible tells the story of a woman that was turned into a pillar of salt near the Dead Sea. Who was her famous husband?", "correct_answer": "Lot", "incorrect_answers": ["Issac", "Abraham", "Pharoah"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the decoding machine called in the motion picture, From Russia With Love?", "correct_answer": "Lektor", "incorrect_answers": ["Vektor", "Sektor", "Hektor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Jane Fonda, Victoria Beckham and Whitney-Houston are celebrities who openly admit to have had this disorder.", "correct_answer": "Eating Disorder", "incorrect_answers": ["Dysthymic Disorder", "Sleep Disorder", "Seasonal Affective Disorder (SAD)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Surprisingly, the number one killer among animals with about 2-3 million human fatalities a year is a tiny insect. Which is it?", "correct_answer": "Mosquito", "incorrect_answers": ["Bee", "Tsetse fly", "Wasp"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which company paid for the first TV ad?", "correct_answer": "Bulova (watches)", "incorrect_answers": ["Dawn (dishwashing detergent)", "Colgate (toothpaste)", "Tide (laundry detergent)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which insect would a myrmecophobic person want to stay away from?", "correct_answer": "ants", "incorrect_answers": ["moths", "bees", "cockroaches"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A day on Venus is equal to how many Earth days?", "correct_answer": "243", "incorrect_answers": ["23", "119", "306"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Venus has the densest atmosphere of the Solar System. What gaseous element comprises the bulk of the atmosphere?", "correct_answer": "Carbon Dioxide", "incorrect_answers": ["Oxygen", "Neon", "Helium"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Did the 1994 movie Forrest Gump win an Oscar for Best Picture?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the official language spoken by the citizens of Sweden?", "correct_answer": "Swedish", "incorrect_answers": ["Finnish and Swedish", "German and Swedish", "Danish"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How old was Dustin Hoffman at the time of filming of The Graduate?", "correct_answer": "29", "incorrect_answers": ["30", "25", "23"]}]